eclipsemc.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy - Eclipse Mining Consortium

## Privacy policy

_Effective: January 6, 2015_

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which BF Labs, Inc., a Wyoming corporation headquartered and doing business in the State of Kansas ("Company") collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of its eclipsemc.com website and any derivative or affiliated websites or applications on which this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, the "Website"). Company reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. You understand that you have the affirmative obligation to check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes, and you hereby agree to periodically review this Privacy Policy for such changes. The continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes an acceptance of those changes. 

**Privacy**  
Company believes that every User should know how it utilizes the information collected from Users. The Website is not directed at children under [13] years of age, and Company does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under [13] years of age online. Please note that the Website may contain links to other websites. These linked sites may not be operated or controlled by Company. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of these or any other websites, and you access these websites entirely at your own risk. Company recommends that you review the privacy practices of any other websites that you choose to visit.  
Company is based, and this website is hosted, in the United States of America. If User is from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law and User is registering an account on the Website, visiting the Website, purchasing products or services from Company or the Website, or otherwise using the Website, please note that any personally identifiable information that User provides to Company will be transferred to the United States. Any such personally identifiable information provided will be processed and stored in the United States by Company or a service provider acting on its behalf. By providing your personally identifiable information, User hereby specifically and expressly consents to such transfer and processing and the uses and disclosures set forth herein. 

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site.   
When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, bitcoin or namecoin wallet ID. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**   
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for failure notification or block processing, may be used to send you information related to block processing, equipment failure, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.   
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then stored in our database. 

**Do we use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information   
We use cookies to help us remember login information and to save your preferences for future visits, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.   
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Correcting, Updating, Accessing or Removing Personal Information**  

If a User's personally identifiable information changes, or if a User no longer desires to receive non-account specific information from Company, Company will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update and/or remove that User's previously-provided personal data. This can be done via the Website or by emailing a request to Company at [office@butterflylabs.com](mailto:office@butterflylabs.com). Additionally, you may request access to the personally identifiable information as collected by Company by sending a request to Company as set forth above. Please note that in certain circumstances, Company may not be able to completely remove a User's information from its systems. For example, Company may retain a User's personal information for legitimate business purposes, if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for account recovery purposes, if required by law or as retained in Company's data backup systems or cached or archived pages. All retained personally identifiable information will continue to be subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy to which the User has previously agreed.

**Contacting Company**  

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please email Company at [office@butterflylabs.com](mailto:office@butterflylabs.com). 

**Your California Privacy Rights**  

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users that are residents of California to request certain information regarding Company's disclosures of personally identifiable information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. If User is a California resident and would like to make such a request, please email Company at [office@butterflylabs.com](mailto:office@butterflylabs.com). 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
